[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart was a prolific composer of the Classical era.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The Beatles originated in Australia.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Beethoven's 'Moonlight Sonata' is a piano sonata.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Elvis Presley is often referred to as the 'King of Pop.'",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Jazz originated in the United States in the early 20th century.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The violin is a percussion instrument.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Bob Marley is famous for his contributions to reggae music.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "A typical full-sized piano has 88 keys.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Mozart composed the '1812 Overture.'",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "The saxophone was invented by Adolphe Sax.",
    "answer": true
  }
]
